Wyck Association Collection 1663-1972 Mss.Ms.Coll.52
American Philosophical Society
- Register to the Microfilm Collection of Wyck Papers
  - Financial Material: JRH, CWH II (Reel 20)
    Box 130 Folder 51 - Box 133 Folder 63
  - Financial Material: CWH II (Reel 21)
    Box 134 Folder 64 - Box 137 Folder 90
  - Financial Material: CWH I, RH III, JBH I, others (Reel 21)
    Box 198 Folder 933 - Box 199 Folder 941A
  - Accounts: CWH I (Reel 21)
    Box OS 1 Folders 1-2
  - Haverford College collection, correspondence of RH III (Reel 22)
    Box HC 1 - HC 2
  - Accounts: RH III (Reel 22)
    Box OS 1 Folders 3-4
  - Inventories: Wyck (Reel 22)
    Box 212 Folder 145
    Box 215 Folders 188, 203
    Box 234 Folder 49
    Box 242 Folders 147 - 148
    Box 244 Folders 190 - 192
  - Estate Material: RH I, CWH I (Reel 22)
    Box 203 Folder 1 - Box 205 Folder 40
  - Estate Material: CWH I, RH III (Reel 23)
    Box 205 Folder 40A - Box 206 Folder 66
  - Estate Material: RH III (Reel 23)
    Box 208 Folders 85 - 93
    Box 211 Folder 126 - Box 212 Folder 145
  - Estate Material: MVWH (Reel 23)
    Box 214 Folder 170 - Box 216 Folder 226
  - Bills and Receipts: CWH I, RH III, others (Reel 23)
    Box 145 Folder 183 - Box 146 Folder 226